Tom Stannett

Engineering Masters Graduate

6 Northfield Shalford, Surrey, GU4 8JN (+44) 7596700788 tom@tm-stnt.dev

PERSONAL STATEMENT

I am a recent Engineering Graduate with a passion for design, art and software development. I have extensive C++ and visual programming (OpenGL) experience, as well as heading many University web design and full stack development projects. I am a quick learner with a keen eye for detail and I am as happy working alone as in a team.

EXPERIENCE

Passion Pictures, London — Runner / IT / Data Entry

SEPTEMBER 2020 - NOVEMBER 2020, MARCH 2021

Role: Runner, basic server maintenance & data entry. Was recently brought back to develop a web scraper for the British Black List project, requiring the use of Python and Selenium. This solution ended up saving the company 3x the cost of doing it manually.

Skills: Python, Selenium, Xpathing(HTML), hardware setup and server configuring.

Natural Interactions Lab, Oxford — *Junior Researcher*

JUNE 2019 - OCTOBER 2019

Role: Research and alpha design of novel prosthetic device for use in developing countries. Spent two weeks in India conducting device alpha testing in partnership with St John's Hospital, Bangalore.

Skills: C++, microcontroller and testbench circuit design, SolidWorks modelling, organisation and administration pertaining to arranging device trials and patients.

EDUCATION

Keble College, University of Oxford Oxford — *Masters of Engineering 1st Class*

October 2016 - JUNE 2020

Specialisations: Machine Learning, Computer Engineering, Statistics, Data Science, Pure Mathematics.

Bachelors Project: Realtime Machine Learning for decoding patient intent

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming: C++, Python, C, OpenGL, TensorFlow Web-dev: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, Node, React, Nunjucks, Jamstack (11ty), Tailwind, SASS/SCSS DevOps: Github, Netlify OS: Arch Linux, Ubuntu, OSX, Windows

NONTECHNICAL SKILLS

Organisation: GitHub, AGILE

Communication: Presenting highly technical information to a non-technical audience.

Flexibility: Experience in working with large well structure teams as well as smaller more agile teams.

VOLUNTEERING

Geovia Eco Commune: A one month residency on a sustainable commune and farm.

for electromyographic prostheses. (C++, Python)

Masters Project: Deep Learned Convolutional Neural Network for solving Simultaneous Localisation And Mapping (SLAM) on a mobile robotics platform using realtime LiDAR data. (C++, Tensorflow, OpenGL, Python).

- Involved working in the perception subgroup of the Dynamic Robotics System Group.
- Required tight version control on GitHub due to the size of the group and codebase.
- Heavy reliance on visualisation of testing data, requiring drawing of complex LiDAR scenes as well as applying realtime interactive transformations - C++, Python, OpenGL, 3D Geometry.
- Due to design requirements, high level of parallelism via threading was required.

Godalming College, Godalming — 4 A-levels and EPQ

SEPTEMBER 2014 - JUNE 2016

A-levels: Maths (A*), Further Maths (A*), Physics (A*), Computing (A*)

EPQ: Hardware Implementations of Neuroplasticity for Machine Learning (A)

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Portfolio (https://tm-stnt.dev)- Find my web design & development portfolio here

Drain Zine (http://www.drainzine.fr)— *University's first counter-cultural online zine*

Pitch: An online zine focusing on counter-cultural elements in fashion, music and art evoking early internet nostalgia through a combination of angelfire-esque visuals and a choose your own adventure format. Drain Zine edition 2 was delayed by Coronavirus and Finals, however is in the pipeline and massively overhauled in terms of visual aesthetic, interactivity, and content.

Title: Co-Founder, CTO, Co-Editor, Writer **Skills Used/Learned:** HTML5, CSS3, Node, 11ty, Jamstack, Google Analytics, GIMP, Submission Editing.

Interests

- I love web development, and enjoy making personal sites for my friends and projects
- I have a deep passion for music, and have been playing guitar for 12 years. I am also self taught on the drums and keyboard, and enjoy producing music in my spare time.
- I love to go rock climbing to keep me fit, street skateboarding and chess.

References are available on request.

re available of request.